on my Discord, Breezy.
That's guy named Breezy joined in and was like,
"Yo, this guy gate keeps man, this guy gate keeps."
So I figured I'd make a video for him
and explain my strategy because I don't think he,
I don't think he understands that I think
he was looking for an FVG [term corrected from context].
But anywho, what I do is I always start
on a four hour timeframe and I just mark
everywhere where a price has broken through
or touched more than once.
So here's our high and then here's this line.
The reason this line is here because look right here,
right here, right here, right there.
Look at all the breakthroughs and our pivots at this line.
Same here, same here, right?
Doesn't gotta be pretty.
Once I have all these lines marked
and I add these manually, like these are manually added.
Once I do this, I go to a one hour, right?
Once we're on the one hour, I specifically wait
for price to break through.
Look, we break and we trade the retest.
We break and we trade, like that's all I do.
I wait for the breaks of my predetermined areas, right?
Always where price has been before.
But what helps me enter?
You're not just waiting for the red line, no, right?
So right now, we broke above our red line.
If I was gonna go for a short play right here,
I would look over here.
Okay, well, what is the Mag 7?
Mainly Nvidia and Apple [name corrected from visible charts], you see how they're kind
of at areas of supply, this one rejected.
I would need to see a full rejection
of supply and start seeing selling.
If I start seeing selling here and selling pressure on here,
I'm going to go short, right?
And what's gonna be my extra piece of confirmation is,
all right, we're near a pivotal area.
We waited for the one hours to come to a pivotal area.
We look at the Mag 7, is it buying?
Is it selling?
Are these also at supplier demand or pivotal ranges?
If that's the case, if I'm looking for a short play,
I would need the VIX to start buying.
Let's get this to a higher timeframe.
Just for extra confirmation, we'll bring it to a 15.
And yup, look, look left, right?
So we're out of pivotal area.
If the VIX is near an area where it pivoted as well,
I'm going to anticipate a pivot, right?
So if we start buying here near a pivotal area,
where near we broke above our pivotal area,
looking left, right?
The VIX starts buying at this pivotal zone.
The NASDAQ will go short.
Only if [first name unclear] and Apple, Tesla, Google, Microsoft,
they start selling, that's my confirmation.
I don't know, it's not clocking to nobody.
So this is for...